designsoak.com 2019-05-06

# Privacy & Cookies / Design Soak Magazine – Design Soak Art & Design Inspiration Magazine

## Notice about Cookies on Design Soak Magazine

The Privacy Policy is located further down this page.

### This site uses Cookies: What are they?

“Cookies” are small pieces of information that a website sends to your computer’s hard drive while you are viewing a website.

### How does ‘Design Soak Magazine’ use Cookies?

Cookies allow us to provide you with a more personal and interactive experience on our websites.

http://www.designsoak.com does use persistent cookies, which stay on your computer or mobile media device even after you have gone offline.

Design Soak Magazine will use different types of cookies at various different pages of your use of our websites, these types of cookies include:

### Essential Cookies

These cookies are essential to the running Design Soak Magazine, such as Session cookies, which enable you to carry out some essential functions on this website like maintaining login details for the session or a transaction. The Session cookies are not stored on your computer and will expire when you close your web browser session.

### 3rd Party Advertising Cookies

Many of our websites carry advertising. A certain amount of this advertising is tailored to the individual user. This “onsite behavioural targeting” uses cookies to discover general information about the pages you visit. The tracking system is anonymised and therefore it does not know who you are; it simply uses the limited information available to it to serve adverts to you, which it believes are relevant.

### Tracking/User Analysis Cookies

Many of our websites also use cookies to track how many individual unique users we have and how often they visit Bauer Media’s websites. We use 3rd party companies for this service such as Google Analytics provided by Google.

### What to do if you want to control the use of Cookies?

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies using your web browser, but please be aware that for some parts of our websites to work you will need to accept cookies. Cookies can be removed or declined by changing your web browser settings. For more information please visit [www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/) and/or [www.youronlinechoices.com](http://www.youronlinechoices.com/). Please be aware that this is 3rd party website and as such Design Soak Magazine accept no liability for the instructions given on this site.

———————————————-

## DESIGN SOAK PRIVACY POLICY

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Soak Design Magazine collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a “User”) of the http://www.designsoak.com/ website (“Site”). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by Soak Design Magazine.

**Personal identification information**

We may collect personally identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, subscribe to the newsletter, fill out a form, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address. Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.

**Non-personal identification information**

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.

**Web browser cookies**

Our Site may use “cookies” to enhance User experience. User’s web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.

**How we use collected information**

Soak Design Magazine collects and uses Users personal information for the following purposes:

  * _– To personalize user experience_  
We may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site.
  * _– To improve our Site_  
We continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you.
  * _– To improve customer service_  
Your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs.
  * _– To send periodic emails_  
If User decides to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time the User would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email or User may contact us via our Site.

**How we protect your information**

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.

**Sharing your personal information**

We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.We may use third party service providers to help us operate our business and the Site or administer activities on our behalf, such as sending out newsletters or surveys. We may share your information with these third parties for those limited purposes provided that you have given us your permission.

**Third party websites**

Users may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website’s own terms and policies.

**Advertising**

Ads appearing on our site may be delivered to Users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile non personal identification information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy policy does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

**Google Adsense**

Some of the ads may be served by Google. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to Users based on their visit to our Site and other sites on the Internet. DART uses “non personally identifiable information” and does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, etc. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>

**Changes to this privacy policy**

Soak Design Magazine has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

**Your acceptance of these terms**

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

**Contacting us**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at:  
Soak Design Magazine  
http://www.designsoak.com/  
DesignSoak {at} andrewkelsall {.dot} om

This document was last updated on June 13, 2011
